Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 11 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [electronics and

Notice Period: 1 Month

instrumentation]

Saptadeep Chanda (1) Featured

Senior Analyst seeking roles in Software Engineering, Software
Development, Application Development, Project Management, Change
Management, Quality Management, Requirement Gathering, Data Warehousing, Unit
Testing, Power Bi, Oracle SQL, Microstrategy, Tableau



Current Designation: Senior Executive

Current Company: Infocepts Technologies

Current Location: Pune

Pref. Location: Kolkata, Pune, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Senior Analyst, Software Developer, Software Engineering, Software Development, Application Development, Project Management, Change Management, Quality Management, Requirement Gathering, Data

Warehousing, Unit Testing, Power Bi, Oracle SQL, Microstrategy, Tableau

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Overall 4.11 years of Experience in the IT industry.

Around 4.9 Years of Experience in MicroStrategy

Trained on Tableau, Power Bi and Informatica

Experience in Working different MicroStrategy Components like MSTR developer, MSTR web, Object Manager, Command Manager

Maintained Positive Communication and working Relationships at all Business Level.

Capable of Working Independently, Manage Small Engagements meeting deadlines as an Individual Contributor and a good team Player.

Work Experience

Infocepts Technologies as Senior Executive

Dec 2020 to Till Date

Accenture as Senior Engineer Application Development

Jan 2016 to Dec 2020

Microstrategy Developer,

Oracle sql, macro

Accenture as Application Developer Senior Analyst

Jan 2016 to Jan 2016

Gathering Requirement from the clients on MSTR Reports, Dashboard, Documents.

Providing Estimation Based on the requirement.

Maintaining Positive communication with the project Team Lead

Proposing improvements in the system and applying it for better performance

Validating and testing the MSTR objects before sending it for Client Validation using Integrity Manager

Creating Unit Testing documents

Raising Case to the MicroStrategy Team.

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=bc7b6ebf7b9ca52d410372ef4cd898c90e0e005543155818074442580c...

Working with the QA team

Creating Microstrategy Reports, Documents and Dashboards.

Creating Schema Objects(eg: Attributes, Facts etc.)

Creating Public Objects(eg: Filters, Metrics, Prompts etc)

Enhancements in existing MicroStrategy Objects.

Working on HPSC Tickets

Creating Freeform SQL reports

Monitoring the Reports and Documents which are scheduled through Narrowcast.

Publishing the Intelligent Cubes

Creating Security Groups, Users, security filter

Creating Event Schedules and subscription.

Maintaining Communication with the Back end ETL team.

Sending Communication emails if there is any delay with report delivery

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (electronics and instrumentation) from Techno India College of Technology, Kolkata in 2015

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Microstrategy Analyst

Microstrategy Certified Architect

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Oracle SQL 12c , MicroStrategy	
VB script, Excel Macro	
Power BI	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Bengali				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time